Welcome to the video friends, the
month of January has started, the
new year of January 2023 and there is
99% possibility that the JF effect is about to start in the insurance sector
and it will start showing you
and it has started today, today
I will show their chart of insurance companies, so
you will see that JF has started, you will
say that brother, what is this GF, if we are
talking about the insurance sector, then
January,
February and March, these 3 together create JF,
which will be the quarterly
van, in these three months you will see that the
prices of insurance companies are on
fire
and this price rise will help you get
excellent returns, okay
friends, so which sector should we talk about,
when we talk about these sectors, there are
two types of insurance, friends, one is
life insurance and the other is
general insurance, okay, there are many
companies that provide life insurance,
many companies provide general insurance, some
companies are listed
in general insurance and some companies are listed in life insurance,
we will talk about private players, you
PSU general insurance, Insurance
Corporation of India, Life Insurance Corporation,
SBI, Life Insurance, ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance and
ICICI Lombard are general insurance.
Okay, this is life insurance. ICICI
Prudence and ICICI Lombard are
general insurance. Bajaj Alliance
provides insurance, but Bajaj
Alliance's insurance company is
not listed in the market yet. So, that means
we will talk about four companies and their
JF effect. Today we will show you
how their prices have started rising
and in the coming 3 months
you can get multi-billion returns. You will
get an opportunity to comment. Friends,
fundamentals. Today I will
not talk about fundamentals, I will only show you the price
chart and how it is
rising. Friends,
before moving forward, first of all I will show you. Done,
okay, hello.
Okay, there
is a 150-day moving average and the rate is
100 days. All
three are considered long-range moving averages.
Friends, now when you look at it,
I have just brought this on the
tape frame chart of HDFC Life. Friends, when you
look at it, this is the month in one period.  In
September 2021, it made its all-
time high of 775, friends, and if we
look from there, it has been steadily rising, at
one time it made a low of
₹500, which
touched it in March 2022. After that, we
tried to understand its upside momentum, it
succeeded many times, then went low, it succeeded many times,
then went low, but right now,
from the month of November, it has
started showing a rise again, then it corrected again
and now see friends, what situation is being created,
I am here to show you
what happens, how the GF effect has
started catching fire in the price, that is what
I have come to show. Now you see, the
price is above today from all three long-range distances,
below the hundred one, last day,
two days, three, four, five, for six days, the price has been
jumping back after touching 100, and
today the price finally opened above 200 days
and finally it
touched the previous resistance and it is excellent.
John Pay gave this close out at 595 and
made a high of 600, which was its previous result of the
month of December itself and
you will see the strength of the price at which it closed, friends,
see all the three moving average prices,
which is called SBI pattern,
friends, this is a 200 day move of
150 and the red one is of 100 days,
friends,
see the last pattern, see here also the
price touched 200 and went up and today
friends,
see, three-four days ago the
price touched here, from there the return is being
made and today finally it updated it, it is
showing a green candle, you saw the
150 day opened at 1225 and finally
touched 1275, gave a close out at 1268
and see, this pattern is being generated,
friends, look at all the companies, for those who want to
invest, the
best company SBI is, you must be aware of how far its wealth is in
India
and every customer of SBI has to
buy SBI insurance, you are becoming
mandatory, the government is also  It
is pushing this thing, so you can
take it for a long term perspective as well, you can also
take it for swing trade for three months, you can also
take it for 10 days, 15 days, 20 days, it is a great opportunity
friends, now our third company about which
I was talking ICICI
Prudential,
it was a little bit the biggest loser
friends because when you look at the T in it, then
look at this,
okay, the
green one day
of 150 and after that
123456 and finally
making a scam, the close out of all its recent
highcope i.e. 460
is given above friends and see the clear direction of C, a
similar pattern is being generated
which
will generate first,
sorry, it is of the life insurance sector, this is a
good thing for the company and at the same time it is
giving an excellent opportunity for swing trade as well, so for this price as well as
for the long term friends,
you have to decide how much money you want to
invest and for how much time period
you want to take entry friends
Okay, now I'm talking about the fourth company,
which is
ICICI General Insurance, or
ICICI Lomd Insurance. This is
general insurance. Okay, again, this
line is for 200 days. The green one is for
150 days, and the red one is for
over 100 days. Okay, this is 150 days.
Look at the price here. It
made a low during this period. Okay,
around June, it didn't touch it. It did so from the last vanishing point,
then you consoled it.
Look at where the price is consolidating. If you
look at the last vanishing point, i.e., from the January point, it is always
touching 150 days around 200 days and then going
back. Okay, here you can see the
price and RS. And finally, today it
made a long police scam.
Whatever high it had made in the month of December,
look here, it has closed above the developed point.
And a similar kind of
formation here. Look at the C, it
appears to be turning upwards. Okay, friends.
So you can buy fresh equity here, you
can buy it for a long term perspective, you
can buy it for 3 months also, how much
amount you will take, how much quantity you will take,
it will be your decision, it was my decision,
I am just suggesting you
that you are going to get a great opportunity in the coming one or two or
three years, so this can
also be a long term investment for you, you should do it yourself by
looking at your risk reward and analyzing your chart,
friends if you
like this video then please like my channel,
subscribe,
share it with your friends and if you have any
question then ask in the comment box,
I will try to reply to it,
friends before investing,
before updating, you will take your decision, do
your research also, only after that there is no
decision to invest, thank you
friends, good night